LEONARD: Hey.
- Leonard, where are you?
(Leonard(running down stairs):)I'm at work.
At 6:30 in the morning?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)On Sunday?
- Why?
- They asked me to come in.
- Well, I didn't hear the phone ring.
- They texted me.
(Sheldon:)Well, as I predicted, I am sick.
(Sheldon:)My fever has been tracking up
exponentially since 2a. m...
(Sheldon:)...and I am producing sputum
at an alarming rate.
[SHELDON COUGHING]
- No kidding.
- Nope. Not only that...
(Sheldon:)...it has shifted from clear
to milky green.
All right, well, get some rest
and drink plenty of fluids.
(Sheldon:)What else would I drink?
Gases? Solids? Ionized plasma?
(Leonard:)Drink whatever you want.
- I want soup.
- Then make soup.
- We don't have soup.
- I'm at work, Sheldon.
[DOG BARKING]